Guide to the James Beard Foundation Archive 1939-2008 (bulk 1990-2008) MSS.214
Fales Library and Special Collections
James Beard Foundation Archive
1939-2008
1990-2008
Fales Library and Special Collections
James Beard Foundation
MSS.214
75 Linear Feet (60 boxes)
The James Beard Foundation continues the work of cookbook author and teacher, James Beard, by offering a variety of events and programs designed to educate, inspire, entertain, and foster a deeper understanding of our culinary culture. The James Beard Foundation Archive represents subject files kept by the Foundation on specific subjects: Chefs, Wine, and Food Writers and Personalities.
Arrangement
The collection retains the original order created by the Foundation. It is broken into three series:
Series I: Chefs
Series II: Wine
Series III: Food Writers and Personalities
Files are arranged alphabetically within each series.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Scope and Content
The James Beard Foundation Archive represents subject files kept by the Foundation on specific subjects: Chefs, Wine, and Food Writers and Personalities. The largerst set of files by far is on Chefs. These files include biographical material, photographs, clippings, and other documents.
Historical Note
The James Beard Foundation continues the work of cookbook author and teacher, James Beard, by offering a variety of events and programs designed to educate, inspire, entertain, and foster a deeper understanding of our culinary culture. Beard was a champion of American cuisine who helped educate and mentor generations of professional chefs and food enthusiasts. Today, the Beard Foundation continues in the same spirit through its programming, which includes educational initiatives, food industry awards, an annual national food conference, Leadership Awards program, culinary scholarships, and publications. In addition to maintaining the historic James Beard House in New York City's Greenwich Village as a "performance space" for visiting chefs, the Foundation has created a robust online community, and hosts conferences, tastings, lectures, workshops, and food-related art exhibits in New York City and around the country.
Provenance
The collection was donated to the Fales Library by the James Beard Foundation in 2008.
Related Materials
James Beard Papers (MSS.263)
James Beard Collection (MSS.139)
Food industry and trade; Culinary industry.; Wine.; Food writers.; Celebrity chefs.; Cooks.; James Beard Foundation; Beard, James, 1903-1985
- Series I: Chefs
  - Aarons, Todd, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abella, David, 1994-1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abowd, Charlie, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abramoff, Andree, 1988-1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Achatz, Grant, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Acheson, Hugh, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Achterfeld, Stefan, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ackard, James, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Acosta, Felix, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Adamo, Roberta, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Adams, Anna and Kevin Macdonald, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Adams, Jamie, 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Adams, Jody, 1994-1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Adams, Patrick, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Adams, Stephen, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Adar, Nir, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Addington, Keene, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Adjey, David, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Adria, Ferran, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Adriar, Chris, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Afentoulis, Emmanuel M., undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Aglibot, Rodelio, 2002-2004 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Agnez, Marcel, 1993-2002 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Agostino, Gabriele, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Aguinaldo, Reggie, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Aharoni, Israel, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Awstedt, Johan, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Aichen, Heinz, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Aielli, Fabrizio, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Aiello, Gabriel, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Akins, Curtis, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Alamilla, Johnny, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Alavazen, Greg, 1997-2005 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Alberg, Brian, 1989-2005 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Alberici, Vincent, 1995-2000 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Alberti, Jean, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Albin, Christian "Hitsch", 1990-2005 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Albrecht, Paul, 1986-1996 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Alchiatore, Antoine, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Alegria, Ruth, 1985-1995 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Alessandria, Bruna, 1997-2001 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Aleveras, Colin and Renee, 1999-2006 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Alexander, Gill, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Alexandre, Isabelle, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Alexandrou, Catherine, 1986-1992 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Alford, Katherine, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Aliperti, Donna and Cathleen Cotter, 1991-1996 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Alix, Thierry, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Allegretti, Alain, 2002-2005 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Allen, Joe, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Allen, Mark, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Aloi, Margherita, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Alonzo, Julian, 1995-2005 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Alpogianis, George, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Altenberg, Michael, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Alterman, Karl, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Altherr, Oliver, undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Althoz, Mitchell, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Amaral, Steve, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Amber, Jeffrey, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Ambrose, Anthony, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Ambrose, Colin, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Amernick, Ann, 1992-1997 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Amex Williamsburg, VA, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Amon, Jack, 1978-1992 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Amorelli, David, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - An, Helene, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Andalo, Natalia, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Anderson, Douglas, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Anderson, Jim, 1989-1997 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Anderson, John, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Anderson, Krista, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Anderson, Tim, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Anderson, Tyler, undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Andersson, Conny, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Andrews, Ann-Michele, undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Andres, Jose R., 1993-2007 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Andrews, Dean - Orient Express Hotels, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Andriola, Tim, 2001-2007 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Angerer, Daniel, 1998-2007 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Anoloh, Elizabeth, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Annis, Neil, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Anthony, Michael, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Antonishek, Joseph, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Antonovich, Matthew, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Antonucci, Francesco, 1990-2002 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Antunes, Joel, 1998-2006 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Anzalone, Salvatore, 1990-1995 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Apicella, Giovanni, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Apicius Cooking Scool, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Appel, Denise, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Apolloni, Shawn, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Appelman, Nate, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Aprile, Claudio, 2003-2008 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Apuzzo, Andrea, 1988-1993 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Arabian, Ghislaine, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Arana, Liz, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Arbeeny, Anthony, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Archivald, Claire, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Aretsky, Ken, 1994-2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Argondizza, Candy, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Armstrong, Cathal, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Armstrong, Govind, 2000-2008 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Armstrong, Jeff, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Armstrong, Tim, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Arnett, Alison, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Arnold, Gail, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Arnold, Sam, 1990-1997 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Aronoff, Deborah, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Aronoff, Eve, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Aronson, Lynn, 1990-1999 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Arpaia, Lello, 1986-1991 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Arpke, Raymona, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Arpken, Peter, 1997-2006 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Arras, Bill, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Artusi, Pelligrino, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Arzak, Juan Mari, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Ascolese, Kevin and Tim Penn, 1991-1997 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Ash, John, 1990-2000 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Ashburn, Sharon, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Asher, Gerald, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Ashlock, Bryan, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Aspell, Brian, 1993-2001 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Assante, Umbarto, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Assouline, Joel, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Assue, Peter, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Assue, Tracy Kamperdyk, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Asti Restaurant, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Atchley, Amanda, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Atkin, Jon, 1986-1994 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Atkins, Lara, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Atkins, Thomas, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Atkinson, Greg, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Attoe, Stephen, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Atwater, Ned, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Aubriot, Eric, 1988-2000 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Auden, Bruce, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Audureau, Jerome, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Auerbacher, William, undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Augustyn, Patrick J., 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Auriana, Angelo, 1990-1997 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Aumeir, Hubert, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Aussignar, Pascal, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Avondoglio, Kirk, 1991-2001 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Awerbuck, Alison, 1995-2006 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Ayala, Alfredo, undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Aycock, Barrie, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Ayers, Mark, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Ayoub, Michael, 1991-2005 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Ayvazian, Ken, 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Azevedo, Manuel, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Aznar, Mariano, 1991-2001 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Azul (Clay Conley and Richard Hales-Somnelier), 2005-2007 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Azumaya, Kazuyuki, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Babcock, Peter, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Babian, James, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Baca, Steve, undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Badman, Charleen, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Baggett, Marisa, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Bagget, Todd, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Bagli, Robert, 1995-1999 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Bahena, Geno, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Bailey, Lee, undated (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Bailly, Jean, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Bainer, Yves, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Bajeux, Rene, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Baker, Flo, 1988-1997 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Baker, Mark, 1991-2001 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Baker, Michael, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Baker, Pilip, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Balassone, Anthony, 1996-2001 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Baldi, Domenico, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Baldwin, Nathan, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Baliani, Daniele, undated (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Ballinger, Melissa, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Balmer, Urs, 1995-2005 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Balzano, Rino, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Banh, Eric and Sophie, 1999-2005 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Banh, Kiong, undated (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Banks, Derek, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Bannos, Jimmy, 1992-1999 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Baratin, Alec, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Barbeau, Monique Andree, 1994-2002 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Barber, Caleb, 1998-2006 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Barber, Dan, 2000-2004 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Barbier, Christophe, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Barbier, Sam/Ralph Yedinar/Waterfront Ale House, undated (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Barcena, Jose "Pepe", 1993 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Barcena, Ileana, undated (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Bardet, Jean, undated (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Bardin, Philip, 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Baretto, Luigi, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Barickman, Donald, 1991-2003 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Barker, Ali and Marcie, 1990-1998 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Barker, Karen, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Barker, Ben, 1987-2000 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Barlow, Richard, undated (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Barnes, Alistair, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Barnes, Brad, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Barnes, Bruce, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Baron, John, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Barral, Robert, 1993-1998 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Barrenchea, Teresa, 1992-1996 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Barrett, James, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Barrigar, Matt, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Barrows, Dick and Sue, 1983-2006 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Barry, Barbara, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Barshak, Alison, 1994-1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Bartoli, Alvaro, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bartoli, Massimiliano, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Bartolome, Riko, 1993-2000 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bartolotta, Paul, 1991-1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Barton, Scott, 1996-2003 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Bashy, Aaron, 1995-2005 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bass, Jo Anne, 1939-1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Bass, Marcia, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Bassalone, Anthony and Leslie, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Bassani, Christiano, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Basson, Trever, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Bassoff, Marcey, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Bastianich, Lidia and Felice, 1992-2007 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Bastianich, Joseph, 1992-2007 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Bastien, Richard, 1984-2002 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Basaulto, Eric, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Batali, Mario, 1992-2003 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bates, Thenawat, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Bates, Wiley, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Battistini, Stefano, 1988-2001 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Baud, Sebastien, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Bauer, Marc, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Baum, Joseph, 1989-1997 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Bax, Marco, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Bay, Andrea, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Bayless, Rick and Dean Groen, 1987-2000 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Baylis, Daniel, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Bazzini, Paul, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Beall, Michelle S., 1989-1996 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Beard, James, 1977-2005 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Bearns, James, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Beaty, Bruce, 1997-2001 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Beaudoin, Philippe, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Beaulne, Michel, undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Beavers, Brent, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Beberman, Peter, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Becerra, Octavio, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Bechler, Gerard, 1993-2001 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Beck, Bill and Wendy, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Becker, Franklin, 1999-2004 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Becker, Jim, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Becker, Neil (New York Restaurant School), 1995 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Becker, William, 1995-2000 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Bedford, Stephan, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Bedoucha, Eric, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Beeson, Jeffrey, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Begina, Jeffrey, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Beischer, Chris, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Belknap, Calvin, undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Bell, Andi, 1998-2001 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Bell, Ned, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Bellanger, Florian, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Belleme, John, 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Bellissimo, Monica, undated (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Benchmark International, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Benevidas, Carlo, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Bencivenga, Matt, undated (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Benet, William "Wilco"--PR Chefs Ayala and Schreiner, 1997-2003 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Bengtsson, Ulrika, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Benitez, Pedro, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Benjamin, David, undated (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Benjamin, John, undated (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Benielloun, Rafih, 1994-1998 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Bennet, Gilat, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Bennett, John, 1985-2002 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Bennett, Jonathan, undated (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Benno, Johnathan, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Ben's Chili Bowl, 1989-2003 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Benson, James, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Benviste, Henn Paul, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Benz, Richard, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Bernardinelli, Francesco, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Bergeron, David, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Bergougnoux, Jean Micel, 1988-1996 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Bergstrom, Al, 1994-2004 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Bergstrom, Bobo, 2003-2006 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Beristain, Guillermo, undated (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Berkowitz, Roger, 1988-1994 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Berlioz, Didier, undated (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Bernal, Paul, undated (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Bernal, Sean, undated (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Bernat, Jean Jaques, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Bernstein, Michelle, 1999-2007 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Bernstein, Sondra, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Bernstein, David, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Berry, Todd, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Berryhill, Ben, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Berthelier, Anraud, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Bertineau, Philippe, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Besh, John, 1998-2004 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bessette, Michael, 1991-1999 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bettig, Pascal, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Beyrouty, Steven (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bianchi, Anne (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bianco, Chris, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Bianco-Anthony, Silvia, 1999-2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bieler, Brian, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bielunski, Marlys, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Bienvenu, Andre Paul, 1987-1999 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Bies, Richard, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Biggid, Caroline, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Bijan, Donia, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Bilger, Michael, 2002-2006 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Billinger, Gehrett, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Biltmore Hotel, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Bimonte, Nick, 1990-2004 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Bina-Seibel, Azita, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Binua, Alvin, 1995-1997 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Biondo, Richard J., 1995-1999 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Birnbaum, Jan, 1989-2003 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Biro, Marcel, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Bistrong, Brian, 2001-2004 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Bitici, Jo, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Bitici, Sergio, 1993-2001 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Bitterly, Ed, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Bittman, Mark, 1994-2001 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Bivins, Tom, 1987-1998 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Black, Mark, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Black, Spencer, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Black, Tom, 2001-2004 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Blackerby, Scott, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Blair, Doug, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Blais, Richard, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Blanc, Georges, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Blanc, Richard, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Blanchard, Ryan, 2002-2005 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Blanchet, Michel, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Blank, Fritz, 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Blau, Elizabeth, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Blau, Matthew, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Blauberg, Erik, 1997-2003 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Blitz, Marty, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Bloise, Michael, 1999-2006 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Blom, David, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Blosser, Sokol, 1999-2005 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Blue, Anthony Dias, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Blumenthal, Dan, undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Blumer, Bob, undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Blythe, Geoffrey, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Boada, Arturo (Solero), 1988-1999 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Bodem, Ian, undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Boccuzzi, Dante, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Bock, Victor L., 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Bocuse, Paul, 1991-1996 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Bogacki, John, 1995-1997 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Bogart, Barbara, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Bogartz, Bruce, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Bogdanow, Larry, undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Boggs, Starr, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Boglione, Matteo, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Bohlsen, Michael, undated (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Boiardi, Hector, 1978-1995 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Boilleaut, Joel, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Boisjot, Patrick, undated (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Boissel, Stephan, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Bojic, Jasmine (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Boland, Matt, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Boller, Marybeth, 1991-1995 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Bollo, Luis, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Bolton, Saul, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Bombaci, Anthony C., 2006 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Bonanno, Frank, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Bon Appetit Magazine, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Bondini, Anselmo, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Bodoni, Pino, 1995-2006 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Bondy, Joanne, 1997-2004 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Bonett, Anthony, 2001-2003 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Bonhomme, Pascal, undated (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Bonnell, Jon, 2001-2004 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Bontempo, Julio, 1988-1992 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Boone, Rob, 2000-2005 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Bordeaux, Michael, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Borel, Alain, 1989-1993 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Borga, Espartaco and Dunio (1 of 2), 2003 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Borga, Espartaco and Dunia (2 of 2), 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - [Borlean, Gary], undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Bortolotti, Giancarlo, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Bosc, Jean-Pierre, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Boswell, Scott, 2002-2004 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Botsacos, Jim, 1997-2007 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Botta, Fabian, 2002-2005 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Bottero, Fabrizio, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Bouchard, Janick, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Bouchon, 2003-2005 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Bouley, David, 1991-2000 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Boulot, Jean Michel, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Boulot, Philippe, 1989-2004 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Boulud, Daniel, 1988-2004 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Bouquin, Bertrand, 2001-2006 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Bour, Nichoals and Lein Schoe, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Bourdeaux, Michel, 1991-1996 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Bourdin, Michel, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Bourkney, Gerard, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Bousquet, Matthew, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Boussand, Mohamed, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Bouterin, Antoine, 1992-2004 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Bowery, Mark, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Bowles, Graham Elliot, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Bowman, Charles, 1989-1993 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Bowman, Sarah French, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Boyce, James, 2000-2005 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Boyd, Karen, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Boyer, Gerard, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Boyle, David H., 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Brachman, Wayne, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Bradley, Bill, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Bracken, Bill (Belvedere), 1993-2005 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Bradley, Jimmy (The Red Cat), 1994-2004 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Bradley, William, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Brand, John, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Brand, Steven, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Brandlard, Laurent, 2001-2008 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Brandon, Scott, 1999-2003 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Brandt, Chirs and Claire Chapman, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Brard, Guillaume, 2003-2005 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Brasel, Sean, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Braverman, David, 1994-1997 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Braun, Margaret, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Braun, Justin, undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Brawley, Boyce, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Brefere, Lisa, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Breiman, Roy, 1994-2006 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Brennan, Eric, 1999-2005 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Brennan, Laura, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Brennan, Dick, 1989-2002 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Brennan, Terrance, 1990-2006 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Brenner, Max, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Briand, Arnauld, 1987-2003 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Brigtsen, Frank, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Briskman, Robert, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Brisson, Michael, 1987-1994 (Box 5, Folder 56)